Hello friends, how are you all at home? I hope
everyone is well at home. I am also doing
well. Today I have a new video for you
on senior citizens.
We will learn about what a senior citizen
is, its definition,
benefits, and why we should get it
for our senior citizens. Friends,
without wasting time, let's start the video about
senior citizens' health insurance
plans. Let's learn about the health insurance plans for senior citizens.
How has the health insurance plan been made for senior citizens? Why has it been made?
Senior citizen health
insurance plans are
kept in a separate scheme.
Its premium is also different and its
benefits are also different.
If there is a benefit attached and its
coverage will also be different.
Available on individual and family
offers.
This is a life insurance from Atmos Productions.
Individuals can take it along with their families and on a
family floater basis as well. It
depends on you and the tax
benefits will also be available on the premium.
Now let us know the definition of senior citizen health insurance.
Senior Citizen Health Insurance
Plans cover medical expenses of
those above 16 years of age.
In the future, your health insurance
covers coverage of the same in
network hospitals
and which hospitals
provide benefits where they have hospitals.
That is, if you have taken insurance from an insurance company, there are
hospitals, if you get your
treatment done in the hospital, it will be cashless and you will
not have to make any payment.
Now we know about the importance of senior citizen health insurance. It is
important that
senior citizen health insurance
for senior citizens reduces the finance
medical expenses.
I have to go to the hostel again and again.
Health insurance is designed in such a way
that it helps them in their
finance
policy. The
insurance
treatment is for them and their condition, that is, for
their health.
Now we will talk about the benefits of senior citizen health
insurance.
What benefits will it provide to us if we get
insurance. The
first benefit of our senior citizens is the Social
Security Medical Program and the second is the
Social Security
Medical Savings Program
System.
Complete senior citizen health
insurance policies are available for
individuals aged between 65 and 80 years.
Senior citizens are available between
65 and 80 years. So, there are different policies for individuals between 65 and
80 years. What premium do you have to pay for it, what
coverage does it have, what will be its
benefits, all this is given in it for travelling, so
you should select it after looking carefully and do
not take it just like that.
Now let us talk about insurance.
Senior Citizen Health Insurance
[Music] reduces
medical expenses. Medical expenses are
reduced by getting the Kundli done.
Insurance policy is designed specially for
elderly people and medical needs insurance.
This was about senior citizens health insurance.
Its definition about benefits is
not important, so subscribe.